(Sheldon:)And there's the clown
that came out of her.
(Sheldon:)I really didn't want
to come here,
(Sheldon:)but this is shaping up to be
(Sheldon:)one of the best Thanksgivings
I've had in a long time.
(Penny:)Me, too.
Hey. Howard says you've
been making fun of him all day!
Now, both of you apologize right now!
(Sheldon:)She's so tiny.
(Sheldon:)It's funny when she's mad.
(Amy:)All right, mister, I think you owe
(Amy:)Howard and Bernadette an apology.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps you're right.
I'm sorry for my behavior.
(Sheldon:)I've had alcohol,
and it's caused me
(Sheldon:)to be inappropriate.
(Bernadette:)-It's okay.
-Don't worry about it.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Ain't she great?
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Now, how's about you get
us a couple of beers?